**Privacy Policy**
==================

**General**
-----------

BulletVPN is first and foremost concerned with user privacy. We want you to be familiar with the various  types of information we do collect and do not collect, in addition to how we collect, store and use any of these types. This Privacy Policy is published to inform you of our practices in connection with the information that we collect through our website BulletVPN.com and by your usage of the BulletVPN service.

**What Information is Collected or Stored**
-------------------------------------------

The defining factor in collecting information relates to what is minimally needed to operate the VPN service and provide you with the service quality that we guarantee and stand by. BulletVPN does not collect logs of any user activity, nor can it link any other collected information to any specific user. We do not collect any logs of user browsing history, connection history, traffic and data transfer, or DNS queries, nor do we store VPN connection logs of any type. That means we do not store the user’s IP address and port, the VPN server’s IP address and port, or the VPN connection attempt, connection establishment or disconnection date and time. This makes it impossible for anyone including BulletVPN to retrieve information about what data content is accessed by a specific user, what specific VPN server was used by a user at a certain date and time, or what source IP address did the user use to attempt and/or establish a VPN connection.

### **General Information**

BulletVPN collects usage information to provide the features offered with the service. Total data consumption is collected to ensure that performance is optimized for all connected users, prohibiting abuse of server resources by individual users. The data consumption metric doesn’t include any trace of accessed or transferred data content through the VPN connection. The number of active connections per user is also maintained during a minimum of one active connection and up to three active connections, without information on the user’s connected devices, their IP addresses and ports, the VPN server’s IP address and port, or the connection establishment date and time.

### **Aggregate Information**

Server connection metadata including server IP addresses, server ports, and server bandwidth metrics from the VPN servers to remote resources are stored in aggregate form without including any user specific related data, in accordance with standard procedures for performance and security analysis in case of events affecting the operation such as but not limited to DDoS attacks and security breaches. This metadata does not include any users’ IP addresses or ports, nor is it tracked or stored in any manner that allows cross referencing to any user account information.

### **Personal Information**

When signing up to the VPN service, user contact and billing information is requested, such as your email address, and payment specific information. The email address is stored to be used for various communication reasons explained in the following section **“Using Information”**, however billing information is never stored. The subscription when (if) created is used for later payments charged solely by the relevant payment processor where available.

### **BulletDNS**

BulletVPN provides its users with BulletDNS, an additional service, bundled with the VPN service subscription, to provide additional support to devices that do not have integrated VPN clients, nor can have third party clients configured. The technical design of the BulletDNS service on devices with such limitations, prohibits the use of the regular username and password method to authorize usage of BulletDNS. As such, users’ IP addresses are used to authenticate the used client devices. BulletVPN users can choose to use BulletDNS by registering the client device public IP address in the SmartDNS page. The IP address is stored for the sole purpose of authorizing the device, without linking it to a VPN user account. Furthermore, we do not collect or store any DNS queries originating from any client device IP address or port, and in that manner users’ browsing activity is completely anonymous, and cannot be retrieved at any point in time.

**Using Information**
---------------------

The collected information outlined in the previous section is solely used to fulfill the purpose of the BulletVPN service delivery. It is used to create and activate a user account, provide a VPN service at optimal quality, ensure proper correspondence with the user, and provide the best possible customer service experience.

As such, we use the email address stored for the following sole purposes:

* To send you notifications related to payments.
* To send you updates and announcements.
* To communicate with you about the VPN service or respond to your inquiries.
* To provide you with links to our website, including password reset links.
* To send you marketing information such as offers and content about matters relevant to the VPN service. You may opt out of these emails, if you don’t wish to receive them.

The aggregate usage information is stored to maintain excellent service functionality. They are used in the following manner:

* Server performance analysis for continuous optimization, such as adding new servers to expand available service resources in a particular location, or to replace poorly performing servers.
* Enforcing preventive and reactive security measurements for protecting users’ privacy.
* Ensuring service is delivered at the promised quality for all users equally.

**Sharing Information**
-----------------------

BulletVPN uses your personal information for the purposes listed in this Privacy Policy. We do not sell, trade, disclose, share or otherwise transfer your personally identifiable information to outside parties or otherwise unauthorized persons.

**Email Correspondence Data**
-----------------------------

When you submit an inquiry by email or through the Contact Form on our website, your email address and correspondence history is saved on third party systems, in compliance with the third party’s agreement to keep this information confidential. This only includes the support platform provided by Zendesk, which is used by BulletVPN to provide customer support.

**Policy Changes**
------------------

We may change this Privacy Policy at any time. Please take a look at the “Last updated” legend at the bottom of this page to see when this Privacy Policy was last revised. Any changes to this Privacy Policy will become effective when we post the revision on this page.

**Contacting Us**
-----------------

If you have any questions regarding this Privacy Policy, or wish to contact us for any reasons in connection with the website or service, please contact us at the following email address: [\[email protected\]](https://bulletvpn.net/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection)

**Last updated: November 10, 2017**

### Support

### Links

### Legal

### Address

Nixworks OU. Reg ID: 12832651

* Narva maantee 5,10117 Tallinn, Estonia
* [\[email protected\]](https://bulletvpn.net/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection)

* 
* 
* 
* 
* 
* 
* 
* 
* 

Copyright © 2024 Nixworks OU. All rights reserved

By continuing to browse the site you are agreeing to our [use of cookies](http://www.aboutcookies.org/). I Understand
